Finding Aid for the John Cope Caldwell Papers MSS.0066
Vanderbilt University Special Collections
John Cope Caldwell Papers
1943-1969
Vanderbilt University Special Collections
MSS.0066a
18.9 Linear Feet
Literature
- Day-books, 1955-1960; 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  General
  14 small and 2 large day-books of Asian, African, and South American travels. Holograph. Three brief autobiographies(1951)- typescript and 2 biographies typescript. Travel schedules- 98 schedules from 1950 to 1962.
- Correspondence - Outgoing, August 3, 1943 - December 1, 1966 (Box 2)
  Outgoing correspondence of 569 letters, chronologically arranged by days and months. Letters are typewritten, carbon copies. Few are mimeographed. 36 undated letters.
- Correspondence - Outgoing, August 3, 1943 - December 1, 1966 (Box 3)
- Correspondence - Incoming (Box 4)
  7 containers. Incoming correspondnece of 3,022 letters, 30 telegrams, alphabetically arranged. Letters are typewritten. with the exception of a few Holograph. Few are carbon copies. There are 196 illegible and unsigned letters.
  - Abbott, Faith (17), Jan. 24, 1956, Aug. 23, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956, Sept. 24, 1956, Apr. 15, 1957, Aug. 5, 1957, Aug. 13, 1957, Oct. 21, 1957, Nov. 6, 1957, Jan. 20, 1958, Feb. 18, 1958, Jan. 8, 1959, Jan. 15, 1959, Jan. 16, 1959, Feb. 25, 1959, March 27, 1959, n.d.
    4
  - Abstine, James, to William H. Bowman (1), Feb. 24, 1956
  - Adams, Betty (1), Dec. 6, 1962
  - Adams, Marie (1), May 30, 1962
  - Ahlers, Margaret A. (1), Nov. 18, 1952
  - Akins, Cheryl (1), May 14, 1962
  - Aley, Ruth (7), Apr. 14, 1953, Apr. 21, 1953, June 16, 1953, Oct. 8, 1953, Feb. 19, 1954, Apr. 2, 1959, n.d.
  - Allen, Clifton J., (2), Apr. 24, 1956, Mar. 25, 1957
  - Allen, Jane (1), Jan. 28, 1963
  - Allerbury, Daisy, to Alfred Kohlberg (1), May 6, 1955
  - Allison, Anne (1), Mar. 18, 1953
  - Aluvihare, Deryck (5), Oct. 9, 1959, Nov. 7, 1959, Jan. 27, 1960, Feb. 12, 1960, Apr. 7, 1960
  - Alvarez, Robert S., to Ralph Wheatley (1), Apr. 28, 1954
  - Ament, Jack, to Lee Keedick Lecture Bureau (1), Sept. 20, 1951
  - Anderson, Carolyn (1), Aug. 13, 1964
  - Anderson, Janet (1), Mar. 26, 1962
  - Anderson, Mitzi (1), Sept. 30, 1959
  - Anisimov, Oleg (1), Apr. 29, 1953
  - Anthony, Joseph (1), Jan. 22, 1954
  - Appelbaum, Howard (1), May 10, 1966
  - Arculli, Robert (28), 1956-1962
    Dates of letters: Mar. 28, 1956, July 24, 1956, Oct. 23, 1957, Apr. 2, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Apr. 27, 1959, May 12, 1959, June 8, 1959, July 29, 1959, Mar. 11, 1960, Mar. 27, 1960, June 17, 1960, July 23, 1960, Sept. 8, 1960, Sept. 24, 1960, Sept. 28, 1960, Oct. 7, 1960, Nov. 17, 1960, Nov. 20, 1960, Dec. 26, 1960, Dec. 30, 1960, Jan. 17, 1961, Mar. 16, 1960, Oct. 12, 1961, Oct. 24, 1961, Oct. 31, 1961, June 7, 1962, n.d.
  - Arens, Richard (2), Oct. 4, 1956, Jan. 31, 1957
  - Armesto, Felipe F., (1), Apr. 26, 1955
  - Arthur, William B. (1), Sept. 23, 1954
  - Asbury, William F. (1), Oct. 31, 1953
  - Baddour, Frank M. (1), Aug. 15, 1959
  - Bahnsen, Elaine (1), Jan. 14, 1963
  - Bailey, James L., to Frank Bass (1), Feb. 14, 1951
  - Bain, Gordon M. (1), Apr. 17, 1959
  - Baker, E. C. (1), July 27, 1964
  - Baker, Harold (1), June 3, 1953
  - Baker, M. E., to Lee Keedick (1), Nov. 18, 1953
  - Baker, Margaret (8), Dec. 29, 1956, Jan. 10, 1957, July 15, 1957, Sept. 13, 1957, Feb. 2, 1959, Apr. 13, 1959, Nov. 19, 1959, Jan. 3, 1962
  - Baker, Mary E. (3), n.d.
  - Baldridge, John D. (1), Sept. 26, 1950
  - Baldwin, Faith (1), n.d.
  - Balgooyen, H. W., to Alice Widener (1), Nov. 23, 1956
  - Ball, Ernest C. (1), May 23, 1955
  - Ball, Gloria M. (1), June 6, 1962
  - Balls, H. O. to Enio Eva, Juan Panayotti, Gilberto H. Aguirre, Juan Parodi, Jose Rodriquez, Cesar Morales, Jose M. Maetinez, and Jose Figueres (8), June 26, 1954
  - Baran, Nicholas M. (1), Mar. 6, 1963
  - Barker, Clothilde (1), Apr. 19, 1955
  - Barrameda, Fred (2), Nov. 3, 1959, June 17, 1960
  - Barrett, Reginald (1), Feb. 18, 1959
  - Barrette, Elise D. (1), Aug. 19, 1957
  - Barry, William F. (1), Oct. 24, 1952
  - Bartlett, Carrie (1), Sept. 20, 1952
  - Bass, Frank E. (1), Aug. 21, 1951
  - Bass, James P. (1), Sept. 22, 1960
  - Bass, W. A. (1), Nov. 12, 1956
  - Bates, Mary N. (1), May 19, 1955
  - Baxter, Charles M. (1), Sept. 19, 1956
  - Beaman, Lucy M. (1), Mar. 22, 1957
  - Beard, Mary L. (1), n.d.
  - Beck, Dewey M., to Lee Keedick (1), May 29, 1951
  - Beckman, Richard W. (1), Nov. 28, 1951
  - Benarfa, Florence V. (1), Oct. 4, 1955
  - Bennett, E, H (2), July 30, 1952, Aug. 8, 1952
  - Bennett, Josiah W. (2), Nov. 18, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953
  - Benson, George S. (1), Jan. 4, 1957
  - Benson, George S./ to Forrest F. Reed (1), Dec. 4, 1956
  - Bentley, Frank R. (1), June 9, 1959
  - Beresford, Donald C. (2), Jan. 22, 1963, Feb. 7, 1963
  - Berman, Sanford, to .John Day Company (1), July 3, 1960
  - Berrean, Sally (1), July 5, 1956
  - Berry, Loren M., to Thomas A. Burke, Alexander Wiley, and "Friend" (3), May 18, 1954
  - Bess, Demaree (1), June 5, 1959
  - Bevis, Palmer (4), June 23, 1953, July 9, 1953, Aug, 3, 1953, Oct. 23, 1953
  - Bey, Betty (1), July 11, 1956
  - Bibb, Mary, B. (1), Apr. 24, 1955
  - Bierly, Ivan R. (2), Nov. 29, 1956, Dec. 28, 1956
  - Billing, Mabel S. (1), Oct. 28, 1953
  - Blancly, Frederich J. 0. (3), Mar. 6, 1958, Mar. 22, 1957, Apr. 14, 1958
  - Blake, Betty (2), Nov. 10, 1958, Apr. 4, 1961
  - Blake, Helen L. (1), Dec. 13, 1953
  - Blochloger, Edna M. (1), Jan. 22, 1961
  - Blossom, John D., to Lee Keedick (1), June 25, 1951
  - Blossom, John D. (2), Aug. 27, 1951, May 14, 1952
  - Boekel, William A. (1), Feb. 18, 1957
  - Booth, Audrey J. (1), Feb. 11, 1953
  - Bosley (3), Mar. 3, 1958, Oct. 22, 1958, Nov. 14, 1958
  - Botter, David, to Lee Keedick, (2), Feb. 17, 1955, July 11, 1955
  - Boughton, W. E. (1), Sept. 30, 1959
  - Bouman, Loenard F. (1), July 27, 1959
  - Bouscaren, Anthony T. (5), Feb. 10, 1956, Feb. 23, 1956, Mar. 13, 1956, Apr. 4, 1956, Sept. 21, 1955
  - Bowden, Joan (1), Nov. 10, 1955
  - Boyce, Ralph L. (2), July 6, 1955, Nov. 24, 1959
  - Boyce, Ray (1), Sept. 13, 1955
  - Boyd, Louise W. (1), Oct. 14, 1952
  - Bradshaw, Ruth (1), Nov. 15, 1960
  - Brandt, Claudia M. (42), 1959-1964
    Dates of letters: Sept. 23, 1959, Nov. 20, 1959, Mar. 4, 1960, May 25, 1960, June 1, 1960, June 2, 1960, Aug. 31, 1960, Sept. 19, 1960, Sept. 27, 1960, Oct. 3, 1960, Oct. 5, 1960, Oct. 11, 1960, Nov. 17, 1960, Jan. 12, 1961, Mar. 13, 1961, Apr. 20, 1961, July 18, 1961, Sept. 8, 1961, Sept. 21, 1961, Sept. 21, 1961, May 4, 1962, May 8, 1962, May 9, 1962, May 16, 1962, May 23, 1962, Junel, 1962, June 14, 1962, Aug. 29, 1962, Sept. 18,. 1962, Dec. 4, 1962, Dec.7, 1962, Feb. 28, 1963, Mar. 18, 1963, May 22, 1963, Dec. 4, 1963, Jan. 3, 1964, Jan. 10, 1964, Jan. 20, 1964, Feb. 3, 1964, Feb. 3, 1964, Feb. 12, 1964, Feb. 14, 1964, July 23, 1964, Aug. 19, 1964
  - Brandt, P. W. (1), Sept. 20, 1960
  - Braniff, Ronnie (1), Mar. 2, 1966
  - Brannon, C. T. (1), May 24, 1963
  - Branscomb, Harvie (2), Sept. 18, 1952, Oct. 2, 1952
  - Breed, Joseph B. (1), Feb. 12, 1954
  - Brent, Ruth (1), Mar. 18, 1956
  - Brewster, Harold N. (1), Apr. 17, 1956
  - Brewster, Dorotyh (1), n.d.
  - Bricker, Ralph 0. (1), Mar. 24, 1952
  - Briggs, Thomas J. (1), Nov. 26, 1956
  - Brines, Russell (14), Sept. 21, 1955, Oct. 11, 1955, Nov. 16, 1955, Nov. 23, 1955, Jan. 31, 1956, Oct. 2, 1956, Oct. 19, 1956, Nov. 30, 1956, Dec. 13, 1956, Jan. 3, 1957, Aug. 7, 1957, Aug. 13, 1957, Nov. 20, 1957, Dec. 10, 1957
  - Brisk, Fay (2), Mar. 12, 1958, Mar. 18, 1958
  - Brockway, George P., to Ruth Aley (1), June 20, 1951
  - Brockway, George P. (1), Jan. 28, 1954
  - Broker, Warren. (17), May 26, 1954, June 2, 1954, June 9, 1954, June 25, 1954, Oct. 12, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954, Oct. 28, 1954, Jan. 4, 1955, Jan. 26, 1955, Mar. 30, 1955, Apr. 15, 1955, Apr. 26, 1955, May 31, 1955, Aug. 3, 1955, Sept. 16, 1955, Oct. 4, 1955, Dec. 12, 1955
  - Brooks, Linda (1), Feb. 15, 1965
  - Brown, E. Robert, to Richard J. Walsh, Jr. (1), July 1, 1959
  - Brown, E. Robert (1), Aug. 21, 1959
  - Brown, Norman N. (3), Dec. 26, 1960, Dec. 30, 1960, Jan. 23, 1961
  - Brown, Wallace O. (1), May 23, 1956
  - Browne, R. A., to Richard Walsh, Jr., (1), July 8, 1965
  - Browne, Robert B. (1), July 8, 1952
  - Bryan, June E. (1), June 13, 1952
  - Bryce, Allan D. (1), May 6, 1963
  - Buck, Pearl S. (1), Mar. 5, 1956
  - Buckley, Maureen L. (1), Mar. 7, 1958
  - Buckley, Pricilla L. (1), May 5, 1959
  - Buckley, William F. (7), Jan. 30, 1956, Feb. 28, 1956, July 18, 1956, June 28, ;957, Apr. 1, 1959, July 28, 1959, Nov. 19, 1959
  - Budlong, M. V. (1), Mar. 5, 1952
  - Budoyo, Sri (1), Nov. 25, 1959
  - Bunis, N. J. (1), Jan. 30, 1953
  - Bunker, Patricia (4), Sept. 9, 1955, Aug. 16, 1956, Aug. 24, 1956, Nov. 24, 1956
  - Bunster, Yolanda (1), Nov. 24, 1960
  - Buol, Susan P. (6), May 25, 1955, Jan. 29, 1960, July 20, 1960, Aug. 16, 1960, Aug. 18, 1960, Dec. 1, 1962
  - Burke, Arleigh, to D. D. Hanson (1), Feb. 20, 1959
  - Burton, William F. to Civic and Church and Auxiliary Groups and Clubs (1)
  - Burke, Coleman (2), Sept. 16, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958
  - Burrell, Elsie (1), n.d.
  - Burris, Miriam (1), Mar. 31, 1960
  - Bussard, Paul (1), Sept. 30, 1953
  - Butler, George N. (1), Apr. 25, 1963
  - Butler, Joan (12), Nov. 9, 1964, Nov. 11, 1964, Dec. 7, 1964, Dec. 8, 1964, Jan. 6, 1965, Jan. 12, 1965, Feb. 5, 1965, Mar. 5, 1965, Aug. 20, 1965, Dec. 2, 1965, Dec. 13, 1965, Dec. 20, 1965
  - Buttinger, Joseph (1), Oct. 2, 1959
  - Byrd, Valdis (1), Sept. 21, 1960
  - Caldwell, Elsie (1), n.d.
  - Caldwell, Harry (1), Apr. 28, 1955
  - Caldwell, John (1), n.d.
  - Caldwell, Kenny (1), n.d.
  - Calkin, K. N. (1), Oct. 23, 1952
  - Callahan, North (2), Apr. 15, 1956, June 5 1956
  - Camesas, Theodora (1), Mar. 24, 1959
  - Camp, Richard W. (1), Aug. 16, 1951
  - Capon, Norma J. (1), Dec. 18, 1957
  - Carder, Clyde D. (1), Apr. 15, 1960
  - Carland, John E. (1), Sept. 29, 1955
  - Carman, J. A. (3), Jan. 13, 1964, Jan. 16, 1964, Feb. 28, 1964
  - Carnall, William H., to Loretta Reidy (1), Sept. 21, 1955
  - Carothers, Neil (1), Apr. 17, 1953
  - Carson, D. D. (2), July 18, 1958, Jan. 28, 1959
  - Carter, Helen (5), Aug. 4, 1954, Sept. 13, 1954, Aug. 5, 1954, Nov. 30, 1954, n.d.
  - Carter, Juliet R. (1), n.d.
  - Cartwright, Frank T. (5), Mar. 12, 1952, June 9, 1953, Jan. 14, 1954, June 8, 1955, Sept. 21, 1962
  - Case, Lillian T. (1), Jan. 16, 1953
  - Cassiday, Bruce (1), July 20, 1955
  - Cazzulino, Arthur (1), Oct. 31, 1960
  - Celliers, Peter J. (3), Oct. 30, 1952, Nov. 23, 1953, Jan. 14, 1954
  - Chadwick, C. S. (1), Jan. 5, 1952
  - Chamberlain, William (1), May 21, 1955
  - Chang-huan, Shan (1), Jan. 12, 1955
  - Chen, Terry T. L. (1), Sept. 21, 1956
  - Chennault, C. L., to Velma N. Tate (1), Aug. 19, 1957
  - Chennault, C. L. (1), Sept. 5, 1957
  - Chih-Mai, Chen (18), 1954-1956
    Dates of letters: Sept. 9, 1954, Sept. 18, 1954, Oct. 22, 1954, Nov 28, 1954, Jan 3, 1955, Jan. 4, 1955, Jan. 7, 1955, Apr. 25, 1955, May 4, 1955, May 25, 1955, June 1, 1955, July 14, 1955, July 21, 1955, Aug. 3, 1955, Aug. 22, 1955, Nov. 18, 1955, July 9, 1956, Oct. 9 1956
  - Ching-Kuo, Chiang (2), n.d., Dec. 26, 1953
  - Chodorov, Frank (3), June 18, 1954, June 24, 1954, July 21, 1954
  - Chow, E. H. (3), Aug. 13, 1953, Aug. 25, 1954, Feb. 27, 1956
  - Christian, James W. (1), Aug. 19, 1960
  - Chun, Sung C. (1), May 9, 1959
  - Cimbolo, Salvatore (1), May 4, 1962
  - Clark, Howard, to Virginia Cain and Forrest F.. Reed (2), May 15, 1953, May 28, 1953
  - Clark, Howard (33), 1953-1955
    Dates of letters: May 13, 1953, May 27, 1953, June 2, 1953, June 8,, 1953, June 16, 1953, June 19, 1953, June 22, 1953, July 1, 1953, July 8, 1953, July 21, 1953, July 21, 1953, Aug. 3, 1953, Sept. 29, 1953, Jan. 14, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Feb. 15, 1954, May 7, 1954, July 15, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 12, 1954, Sept. 13, 1954, Oct. 4, 1954, 0ct. 6, 1954, Oct. 14, 1954, Oct. 14, 1954, Dec. 23, 1954, Jan. 4, 1955, Apr. 28, 1955, Sept. 8, 1955, Nov. 9, 1955
  - Clark, William A. (1), June 24, 1953
  - Clarke, Helen (1), May 28, 1956
  - Clarke, J. Calvitt, to Richard Walsh, Jr. and John T. Gibson (5), Mar. 26, 1956, June 1, 1956, Aug. 28, 1956, Sept. 5, 1956, Nov. 26, 1956
  - Clarke, J. Calvitt (6), Apr. 25, 1955, Apr. 12, 1956, May 28, 1956, Apr. 20, 1959, n.d.
  - Clarkson, Helen (3), Jan. 15, 1958, Jan. 23, 1958, Feb. 6, 1958
  - Clement, Frank G. (1), May 20, 1966
  - Close, H. M. C. (1), Nov. 6, 1957
  - Cochrane, Joanna (1), Nov. 13, 1957
  - Cohen, Donna R. (1), June 5, 1952
  - Cohn, Roy M. (1), Mar. 3, 1953
  - Coillie, P. (1), n.d.
  - Colclough, Elizabeth S. (5), June 13, 1951, June 18, 1951, June 21, 1951, June 29, 1951, Mar. 6, 1952
  - Coleman, Hara L. (1), n.d.
  - Coleman, J. Winston, to Forrest F. Reed (1), Mar. 18, 1955
  - Collado, Jose' Moguel (1), May 2, 1963
  - Coller, Edward W., (5), Oct. 7, 1952, July 14, 1954, Mar. 22, 1955, July 22, 1956, Sept. 8, 1957
  - Collins, Louise E. (1), Feb. 10, 1956
  - Combs, Betty (2), Jan. 23, 1959, n.d.
  - Conlon, Edward J (3), Sept. 15, 1958, Jan. 27, 1959, Feb. 25, 1959
  - Conrad, Bettye (1), n.d.
  - Conway, Peggy (1), n.d.
  - Cook, Jim (1), Mar. 11, 1957
  - Cook, Maude H. (1), Oct. 7, 1952
  - Cool...., Monaca (1), n.d.
  - Cooley, Bernard H. (1), Aug. 14, 1953
  - Cope, Quill E. (2), Nov. 5, 1956, Nov. 9, 1956
  - Copeley, Helen M. (2), May 22, 1953, Mar. 23, 1956
  - Cornuelle, H. C. (2), Mar. 12, 1953, Mar. 20, 1953
  - Corrigan, Kevin, to Pyo Wook Han, Walter L. Seaman, and Anson C. Lowitz (3), July 25, 1952, Oct. 22, 1952, Feb. 26, 1953
  - Corrigan, Kevin (38), 1952-1953
    Dates of letters: June 24, 1952, July 25, 1952, Sept. 10, 1952, Sept. 17, 1952, Sept. 23, 1952, Oct. 2, 1952, Oct. 10, 1952, Oct. 17, 1952, Oct. 20, 1952, Oct. 22, 1952, Oct. 27, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952, Oct. 30, 1952, Nov. 12, 1952, Nov. 13, 1952, Nov. 18, 1952, Nov. 18, 1952, Nov. 20, 1952, Nov. 21, 1952, Dec. 5 1952, Dec. 11, 1952, Dec. 30, 1952, Jan 2, 1953, Jan. 5, 1953, Jan. 9, 1953, Jan. 16, 1953, Jan. 20, 1953, Jan. 22, 1953, Jan. 23, 1953, Feb. 9, 1953, Feb. 23, 1953, Feb. 25, 1953, Feb. 26, 1953, Apr. 6, 1953, May 4, 1953, May 19, 1953, June 9, 1953
  - Courtenay, Walter R. (1), Dec. 20, 1952
  - Coverdale, J. S. (2), Mar. 22, 1957, June 3, 1957
  - Cowan, L. W. (3), Aug. 22, 1960, Sept. 6, 1960, Nov. 2, 1960
  - Cox, Helen (1), Feb. 19, 1960
  - Crafts, Ralph (1), Oct. 9, 1956
  - Craipain, G. M. (1), Aug.13, 1959
  - Crawford, Paul (1), Nov. 15, 1955
  - Cromelin, Marie A., (1), May 6, 1963
  - Cronin, John F. (3), Oct. 13, 1955, Oct. 19, 1955, Nov. 9 ,1955
  - Crooks, Thomas E. (3), May 22, 1957, June 14, 1957, July 3, 1957
  - Crossman, Julie.,- (4), May 24, 1954, June 15, 1954, July 12, 1954, Aug. 17, 1954
  - Crounse, Laura H., to Elizabeth Schenk (3), Feb. 4, 1953, Mar. 4, 1953, May 18, 1953
  - Crounse, Laura H. (5), Feb. 4, 1953, Feb. 17, 1953, Apr. 5, 1953, Jan. 25, 1957, n.d.
  - Crowe, Thomas G. (4), Feb. 8, 1954, Feb. 17, 1954, Mar. 16, 1954, Sept. 17, 1956
  - Cutwell, Hugh (1), n.d.
  - Daly, Gerald R. (2), Nov. 20, 1950, Jan. 18, 1951
    5
  - Daly, Thomas F. (10), July 3, 1957, July 10, 1957, July 15, 1957, Aug. 1957, Aug. 12, 1957, Aug. 19, 1957, Aug. 27, 1957, 10, 1957, Sept. 12, 1957, Oct. 9, 1957
  - Daniel, Marjorie L. (1), Feb. 5, 1955
  - Dank, Leonard D. (1), Nov. 1, 1960
  - Dashiell, Alfred S. (1), Sept. 3, 1954
  - Daumarie, Y. (1), Jan. 27, 1959
  - Davies, Susan A., to Lee Keedick (1), Nov. 19, 1954
  - Davies, Thurston (2), Dec. 19, 1950, Nov. 4, 1953
  - Davies, William (1), Dec. 25, 1956
  - Davis, Louise (1), Mar. 22, 1960
  - Davis, Malcolm (1), Dec. 23, 1957
  - Davis, Robert (1), Aug. 3, 1952
  - Day, John (2), Oct. 13, 1961, Aug. 17, 1966
  - de.Beausset, Connie (1), Mar. 21, 1954
  - Debo, Angie (1), Mar. 29, 1954
  - de Grosbois, Roly (1), Dec. 12, 1963
  - DeJong, George, to Christian Herald Editor (1), n.d.
  - De Vault, Doris (3), July 5, 1957, Apr. 2, 1960, July 7, 1961
  - Dewire, Ethel, to Loretta Reidy (1), Oct. 26, 1955
  - Dewire, Ethel (1), Nov. 5, 1955
  - Delaney, Robert F. (1), May 24, 1963
  - Dell, Joan (1), Nov. 10, 1953
  - Dey, Robin (1), Apr. 2, 1956
  - Dick., Sarah (2), July 6, 1962, Aug. 18, 1963
  - Dixon, Jeanne T. (1), Oct. 29, 1953
  - Dodd, Margaret (2), Feb. 8, 1963, Feb. 20, 1963
  - Donlevin, Robert (3), May 4, 1954, June 3, 1954, June 25, 1955
  - Donner, Francine Me (1), Oct. 19, 1956
  - Donovan, Thomas J., to Haller Lewis (1), July 3, 1959
  - Dorn, Frank, to Henry Regnery (1), July 23, 1953
  - Dorn, Frank (1), July 24, 1953
  - Doss, Lilyan (1), n.d.
  - Dowling, William J. to Reader's Digest (1), Jan. 9, 1957
  - Dowling, William J. (1), Jan. 31, 1957
  - Dozier, Daisy (1), Dec. 10, 1957
  - Draper, John L. (1), July 8, 1952
  - Dresser, Amos (1), Feb. 10, 1954
  - Drew, Charles W. (1), Nov. 12, 1959
  - Du Buque, Jean H. (1), July 2, 1959
  - Due, Nguyen Phu (1), June 30, 1959
  - Dudleston, Joseph (2), June 2, 1959, Mar. 26, 1964
  - Duff, J. Arthur (2), Jan. 7, 1963, Jan. 19, 1963
  - Dugdale, Grant (3), Mar. 3, 1955, Mar. 7, 1955, Mar. 22, 1955
  - Dumasia, Behram P. (2), Jan. 29, 1960, Sept. 2, 1960
  - Duncan, Gorgan B. (1), Feb. 6, 1953
  - Dunlop, H. P. (1), July 5, 1951
  - Dunn, Thomas (1), July 31, 1965
  - Duvall, Jo (1), July 22, 1955
  - Early, Robert P. (1), June 24, 1954
  - Edmonds, Mildred (6), Dec. 11, 1956, Nov. 30, 1956, Jan. 31, 1957, Oct. 21, 1957, Nov. 19, 1957, Dec. 31, 1957
  - Edwards, Clyde S. (1), June 18, 1952
  - Egger, Patt (1), Oct. 7, 1955
  - Einhorn, Rose D. (1), Dec. 3, 1959
  - Einhorn, Paula (1), Sept. 26, 1961
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (1), Sept. 7, 1956
  - Eldridge, Kenneth T. (1), Mar. 16, 1965
  - Eliot, T. S., to Charles Lowry (1), Dec. 12, 1956
  - Ellinwood, Margery L. (1), Oct. 15, 1951
  - Elliot, James A. (2), Aug. 17, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956
  - Elliot, Norman K., to Mrs. George E. Maynard (1), May 8, 1956
  - Elliott, William Y., to Charles W. Lowry (1), Aug. 5, 1957
  - Ellis, C. M., to Lee Keedick and Loretta Reidy (2), Oct. 10, 1950, June 21, 1958
  - Elmguist, Ruth M. (2), Nov. 16, 1953, Nov. 20, 1953
  - Embry, Carlos B. (1), Aug. 4, 1956
  - Engebretson, Rae (4), Apr. 18, 1955, Jan. 27, 1959, Mar. 14, 1960, n.d.
  - English, James W., to Richard Walsh (1), May 21, 1956
  - English, James W. (1), July 15, 1955
  - Epstein, Albert S. (2), Mar. 8, 1957, Apr. 1, 1957
  - Erman, Dick (2), Apr. 24, 1955, n.d.
  - Ernst, Philip W. (1), May 3, 1963
  - Eton, Suh (1), Nov. 4, 1952
  - Evans, Helen F. (2), Apr. 16, 1951, Apr. 25, 1951
  - Ewald, Barbara (1), May 28, 1962
  - Ewing, Anne 0. (1), n.d.
  - Ewing, Cornelia K. (1), n.d.
  - Eyestone, J. Bruce (1), Feb. 4, 1954
  - Eyre, Dean J. (1), n.d.
  - Fagen, Beverly (1), Mar. 1, 1965
  - Fahmy, Susan D. (1), June 8, 1956
  - Fallis, William J. (1), Jan. 4, 1955
  - Farolan, M. (1), Oct. 19, 1959
  - Fawcett, Eugenia (9), Oct. 28, 1953, Oct. 19, 1954, Nov. 26, 1954, Jan. 26, 1955, Mar. 1, 1955, Apr. 1, 1955, Apr. 6, 1955, May 5, 1955, June 25, 1957
  - Federico, Grace (4), Sept. 17, 1965, Dec. 7, 1965, Dec. 9, 1965, Dec. 15, 1965
  - Feldman, Harvey (1), Aug. 26, 1954
  - Felt, George E. (1), Mar. 22, 1963
  - Fenton, R. W. (1), Jan. 8, 1962
  - Fideler, Raymond E., to Richard J. Walsh, Jr. (1), Feb. 11, 1959
  - Fielder, Gerald L., to Saturday Evening Post (1), Sept. 5, 1961
  - Finnely, John W. (1), Oct. 23, 1952
  - Fisher, Dorothy C., to Lesley (1), June 3, 1953
  - Fisher, Ralph H. (1), Sept. 26, 1950
  - Fitzgerald, Roy G. (1), Nov. 29, 1957
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas F. (1), May 18, 1954
  - Flanagan, Francis D. (1), Feb. 27, 1953
  - Flanagan, John C (1), Mar. 31, 1959
  - Flanigan, J. P,, to Janet Schoelles (1), Oct. 24, 1952
  - Fleischman, Merlene (1), Mar. 26, 1961
  - Fletcher, Archie G. (3), Apr. 27, 1954, Feb. 4, 1959, Sept. 26, 1959
  - Fletcher, Donald R. (5), Sept. 20, 1960, Nov. 17, 1960, Jan. 23, 1961, June 14, 1962, n.d.
  - Fletcher, Martha (1), Jan.4, 1954
  - Floyd, Louise P. (7), Sept. 2, 1953, Sept. 23, 1953, Sept. 29, 1953, Oct. 5, 1953, Oct. 7, 1953, Oct. 23, 1953, Oct. 23, 1953
  - Floyd, Robert L. (2), Aug. 16, 1952, Aug. 20, 1952
  - Fockler, Shirley (5), June 21, 1960, Jan. 2; 1963, Jan. 24, 1963, Mar. 18, 1954, Mar. 30, 1964
  - Fogle, Cindy R. (1), Mar. 28, 1962
  - Forbes, Sally (1), Mar. 14, 1961
  - Fore, William F. (1), Feb. 16, 1959
  - Forrestal, James, to Elsie I. Fletcher (Caldwell) (1), Feb. 17, 1946
  - Foschini, Bernard M., to Father Mannion (1), Aug. 2, 1957
  - Foschini, Bernard M. (8), Dec. 12, 1956, Dec. 26, 1956, Dec. 30, 1956, Jan. 11, 1957, Aug. 2, 1957, Aug. 16, 1957, Aug. 24, 1957, Dec. 5, 1957
  - Foster, Donald C. (2), Oct. 8, 1959, Oct. 26, 1959
  - Foster, Paul (1), July 16, 1959
  - Fowler, David M. (1), July 27, 1953
  - Fowler, Virginia (1), July 21, 1955
  - Frank, Helen (1), Nov. 30, 1964
  - Frankenhoff, Laura B. (1), Apr. 28, 1959
  - Franklin, Charlotte (1), May 31, 1962
  - Franks, Maurice R. (4), Jan. 17, 1955, Feb. 21, 1955, Apr. 21, 1955, Apr. 27, 1955
  - Frazier, Bernard W. (1), Jan. 26, 1959
  - Frey, Joseph R. (1), June 22, 1951
  - Frillmann, Paul W. (1), Mar. 15, 1956
  - Frost, Lesley (1), n.d.
  - Fulton, Jane (1), Mar. 3, 1958
  - Fu-sung, Chu (4), Aug. 2, 1956, Aug. 9, 1956, Dec. 12, 1956, Dec. 22, 1956
  - Gade, Wallace A., to George Johnston (1), Sept. 27, 1956
  - Galub, Jack (4), May 13, 1959, May 26, 1959, June 10, 1959, June 11, 1959
  - Gamby, Ray (1), May 30, 1959
  - Gammon, James P. (1), May 28, 1948
  - Gantz, Shirley, to John Day (1), Apr. 6, 1960
  - Garcia, Louise (2), July 10, 1960, Aug. 12, 1960
  - Gardner, Dorothy B. (1), Sept. 6, 1956
  - Gardner, John (1), Oct. 9, 1952
  - Garside, B. A. (1), Feb. 14, 1959
  - Garvey, Neil F., to Lee Keedick (1), July 16, 1952
  - Garvey, Neil F. (2), July 11, 1952, July 16, 1952
  - Gaucher, A. Ernest (1), Feb. 25, 1957
  - Gaudion, D. A., to Elizabeth Schenk (1), Nov. 9, 1950
  - Gault, Alma E. (2), Oct. 14, 1953, Nov. 25, 1953
  - Gay-Tuff, E. (2), Mar. 19, 1955, Sept. 30, 1955
  - Gdams, Uniola (1), Jan. 1, 1958
  - Gebhardt, Irene (1), Jan. 26, 1954
  - Geppert, G. E. (1), Mar. 16, 1951
  - Gibson, Ellen (1), Sept. 15, 1960
  - Gibson, John T., to James Michener (1), July 9, 1957
  - Gibson, John T. (14), Oct. 17, 1955, Sept. 21, 1956, Dec. 31, 1956, Feb. 1, 1957, Feb. 20, 1957, Mar. 7, 1957, Mar. 12, 1957, Apr. 29, 1957, May 6, 1957, May 20, 1957, July 12, 1957, Aug. 2, 1957, Oct. 22, 1957, Feb. 2, 1959
  - Gibson, Russell, to U. S. A. (1), Dec. 28, 1957
  - Giga, Seiji (3), Aug. 18, 1958, Sept. 9, 1958, Nov. 12, 1958
  - Gil, Lois M. (1), Sept. 12, 1955
  - Giles, Lewis (1), Jan. 30, 1959
  - Girson, Rochelle (1), Sept. 27, 1960
  - Glass, Carter, to Ralph Wheatley (1), June 16, 1954
  - Glass, Mildred D., to Reader's Digest (1), Mar. 4, 1957
  - Glover, Fay W. (4), May 14, 1963, Aug. 23, 1963, Oct. 13, 1964, Sept. 28, 1965
  - Goldberg, Hy (1), Jan. 2, 1955
  - Gomane, Andre' (1)
  - Goodfellow, M. Preston (1), July 29, 1953
  - Gordon, Horace (1), Jan. 9, 1958
  - Gossard, J. Earl (1), Apr. 6, 1955
  - Gossett, Jane (1), Nov. 6, 1956
  - Gouffe, N. F. (2), Jan. 8, 1963, Jan. 16, 1963
  - Gould, Randall (3), June 16, 1952, Feb. 21, 1954, n.d.
  - Graeser, Mary L., to Sir (1), Dec. 10, 1956
  - Graham, Eleanor (1), May 19, 1960
  - Gras, Gloria (2), Feb. 22, 1955, Mar. 21, 1955
  - Gregersen, Magnus I. (5), Dec. 12, 1955, Oct. 10, 1956, Dec. 5, 1956, Feb. 25, 1957, n.d.
  - Green, George F. (1), May 17, 1955
  - Green, Var M. (1), Feb. 28, 1968
  - Greene, Adron (2), July 9, 1959, Sept. 25, 1959
  - Greene, John L. (2), Apr. 21, 1955, May 6, 1955
  - Greene, M. C. (2), June 5, 1956, Aug. 2, 1956
  - Greene, Mary V. (1), May 25, 1953
  - Greenfield, Margarette (1), Oct. 22, 1957
  - Grisson, Alice, to Lee Keedick (1), Nov. 15, 1953